What's up?
What's up people?
The golfer's up there, looking down on us.
I'm not sure how I feel about that.
Imagine he's playing golf and we get a golf ball in the head.
You know, it wouldn't surprise me if this game had a weapon like that.
You know, you've hitting golf balls and that's how you deal damage.
Because this game is silly.
And would you look at my inventory?
Fucking clean.
Did that last time.
So now I'm ready to explore.
Let me quickly check here.
Everything is properly organized.
Look at that.
We got keys, we've got potions, a heart lantern if needed.
So that's awesome.
Hano, what are you doing here?
You still sell me crap?
That's okay.
I am gonna go down again into the deep to find more titanium and other things.
Because I want to craft things with the new stuff.
But I'm not done finding things.
Hold on, maybe I should not dig here.
Not there.
Somewhere else.
Where have I not sort of dug yet?
Maybe I can continue this right here.
Hey, stop that.
Yeah, I'm gonna do that.
I want to go caving.
Because I'm not... Also, we need more of that living soul.
Or soul of living.
I actually forgot the name of it.
Something like that.
Or soul of light, I think it was called.
Because there's also a soul of night.
Or essence.
It's one of the two.
And I want to find them all.
By the way, this weapon right here is the best so far.
The mythical flower of fire.
Kind of an incredible weapon.
Hold on, I need to turn the game down a bit.
Test.
Okay, that's better.
Actually turn it a little bit.
Just like that.
Beautiful.
I'm gonna dig here.
It's exploring time!
Actually, there's a flower I need to get more of, which is...
What is the name of it?
It's the one I need for... Spelunker potion.
I forgot the name of that flower.
But it's something that I don't have enough of.
Where will I emerge?
Okay, we're safe.
Dude, I love just digging and not knowing where I end up, you know?
It's a cool feeling.
Whoops!
What was that?
Oh, it was a worm, I think.
Look at the pieces lying around.
It got hit by the stars and died instantly.
Okay, there's nothing over there.
Come on, show me that titanium.
Okay, this is where I've already been.
But that's nice.
Maybe there's some titanium here.
Let's just look.
The titanium is sort of colorful.
What's that?
What is that?
Oh, a bit of Calcum.
Nice.
I don't see anything here.
This is where I was at some point and then I didn't go further.
Blink?
No, blink rune is not the one.
There's another one.
Lumen... something.
I was about to say lumen flower, but that's... that's the wrong game.
What's that?
Platinum.
Is there anything up there?
Yeah, I'm not sure about that.
Let's go a little further down.
Oh, wait, wait.
Oh, I'm confused.
I'm also feral bite.
Increased damage, decreased life regen.
Wait, increased damage as in I do more damage?
No way, right?
Whoopsie.
Okay, that's scary.
I have to remember these There we go.
Get out of here.
Also, I have amazing healing potions now.
I actually forgot where I got them.
I think I bought them.
Or was that the mana ones?
What is this?
Another strange plant.
This one looks different.
It's related to dying.
Yeah, I don't see any ore.
Oh, lost girl.
Oh, nymph.
You're evil.
Evil.
I got her.
Deceiver of fools.
Huh?
Oh, no, I didn't click on it.
Okay, here we go.
Kill a nymph.
What did you have?
Wait, the metal detector!
That's the one I wanted!
No way, how does it work?
Wait,
cobalt.
Okay, okay, I was kind of expecting the the ore to light up similar to spelunking potion.
So like a replacement for the spelunker potion, but it's not quite the same as it.
Or a calcium detected nymph.
So I guess it's just closest to my position, right?
Oops.
That would make sense to me.
That's amazing.
And here it's cobalt detected.
So somewhere here there's ore calcium, maybe down.
It's gonna be a little hard to know though.
It's like one of those hotter, hotter, colder, colder situations.
It's near... okay, this is not actually as helpful as I thought it Am I crazy?
This is not that good.
This sucks!
I don't know, I'll have to experiment more of it with it, but it just seems like it could be in any direction, right?
Like in 360 around me.
Also there's an enemy here.
Hey, show yourself.
Gotcha.
Okay.
So where do I go now?
Actually, I'm gonna keep going down over there.
Here.
Hey!
You know what?
Actually the fire?
Wait a minute.
How did this work again?
Look, you can sort of scout using this weapon.
Look, the light goes through.
You can totally use that to scout.
Yo, that's crazy good.
Ah,
that's actually awesome.
Oh, here we go.
Ory Kalvgum.
Actually, I think I have a lot of that now, but I need the Titaino.
I want that part, gimme.
Bombs!
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Hey!
Oh, come on.
I just automatically used the mana potion.
I heard it.
I will take all the coble.
Sup, dude?
God, this weapon is good.
What did you drop?
Oh, nothing.
It looked like a handgun.
Okay, and then down here.
Man, when you hit enemies, you can totally scout.
Actually, you can scout without hitting enemies.
The sparks, I don't know Let's see, if I keep doing this.
No, I need to be further away from it, I think.
Yeah, look, there worked.
And again, aha!
So the further away you are, then the spark will go through.
Alright.
Alrighty then.
Get out of here.
I love exploring these caves.
It's the best.
It looks like a giant bat.
Okay, it's a giant bat.
I thought it was a cobalt bat.
Weather down.
I kind of want to connect to the cave on the left.
You know what, let me put this on again.
Oh, it's the damage thing per second.
Wait a minute.
Oh, I don't need to have it on!
Look!
I don't even need it!
It's still the... Ah-ha!
Ah-ha!
Well, well, well!
That's nice.
So, hold on, there was Orykalka.
Okay, you know what, I'm just gonna keep going until it says titanium detected nearby, and then I go nuts.
I have a strategy for this now.
Just watch.
It's gonna be crazy.
Still Orykalkum.
Ah!
Wait, let me take that actually.
So, if I remove this now, will it change?
Okay, so that means there's more.
What is that?
Is that crimp tape?
50th giant bat.
That's not that many.
Oh, I remember the name of the plough now.
Moon something.
Moon glow or something.
That's the flower I need, and I forgot where I got it.
You know what, actually, I think I get it here.
It's sort of a blue flower.
Maybe I'll make my way there, just to see.
Let's confirm that actually.
Because I also want to get some more of those seeds for that, so that I can grow them.
Orykalkum nearby.
Nice.
Show me the titanium.
Ooh, here we go.
I gotta say, though, this thing is way slower than the magic missile.
It feels slow as hell.
But I guess the DPS is bigger.
We tested it, so...
Yeah.
Strange plant.
So, is that a really rare thing?
Let's see if we can find that.
So, it actually prioritizes that over the cobalt, even.
Interesting.
So, strange plant, huh?
It's a big deal.
Wait, no, it's just Orykalkum.
So, here somewhere.
Maybe up.
Actually, let me check.
Oh, do you see that?
Wait a minute, I need to be here.
I don't know about the strategy.
Where's the strange plant?
Fucking... Oh, what's this?
Come on, get up there.
My god, I can't see what I can break and not break.
Oh, I'm losing my mind.
Please die.
There we go.
Cobalt nearby.
Oh, the metal detector is kind of bad.
It's totally shit.
It's got nothing on the potion.
It's not even close.
Here we go.
Tungsten.
Oh man, it's so blue.
Wow.
Live crystal.
Glowing mushroom.
Hold on, the color is actually going to mess with my ability to distinguish ores in here.
Like, what is this down here?
I think that's platinum.
Yeah, okay.
At least I got that right.
Uh oh.
We're fine.
Oh, that's silk.
Let me grab a bunch.
Okay.
Dude, it says, Orykal can detect the nearby everywhere.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, I think that's... Hold on, I can see it on the map, no?
Lead.
Okay.
We just did so much damage.
Was it user?
I'm gonna go deeper, because I think we need to go really deep to find the Hidainu.
What the hell is that?
Spore skeleton.
Look at little HPS.
Ah, whatever.
We get to live.
Why can't I...
What the... Ah, I see.
Something was blocking me.
So, I've been here before, but not after I unleashed things.
Give me all of this.
I actually don't know what I'm supposed to use the Orykalkon.
Actually, it's already better than the gear I have, right?
I can make Orykalkon gear, at least.
And I think I have enough to do that by now.
I have a lot of it.
And I mean a lot.
But it would be cool to skip that and go straight to the titanium.
Because if I'm gonna be switching it up anyway, you know, what's the point?
Oh, it's dark.
Oh, where am I?
Okay, we're fine.
What do I see?
Orykalkon.
It should prioritize titanium, right?
Even if there's Orykalkon?
That's what I think.
There's an armored skeleton there.
Oh my god, so much HP.
Let's drain it.
I can't see shit.
Cobalt nearby.
Come on.
Where am I even?
Oh, that's a topaz.
I thought it was a button.
Drain it all.
I should have brought some glow lights.
Maybe I have some.
I don't.
What?
Titanium to take the nearby.
Oh god.
Oh, there's a boulder there as well.
Come on.
There we go.
Oh god.
Why is there so much water?
I should not have drained.
Why do I drain?
I have glow sticks.
Blow it up.
Everything.
Okay, that's good.
Get some air.
Let's go.
Now, where's the... So, titanium here.
Not there.
It's sort of here.
Let's look for it.
In fact, I'm gonna go here and do this.
Why can't I shoot?
Titanium?
Not there.
Okay, that's a little bit hard to see.
Strange plant in here now.
There's a... Ah, boulder!
Oh, saw that just in time.
Still didn't avoid it though.
Bro, where is this titanium?
Is it up here?
Drainage.
Okay, so this is cobalt.
Titanium is here.
Is it right below me then?
I can't see shit.
Do I have any vision potions?
Wait a minute.
What is that?
Floating... I'm dying.
Floating.
Gross.
I gotta heal here.
Holy shit.
How am I not dead?
Heal me.
Okay, it's a little bit of an increase there.
All right.
So, titanium here.
So, hold on.
If I go to the left here, it says cobalt.
Man, this sucks.
I need spelunker.
Bro, this metal detector... Oh, fuck.
This metal detector is terrible.
You know what?
It's actually distracting me right here.
I think this is making me find less of it.
Because I, you know, I go razor focused trying to find it, and I just spend an eternity not finding shit.
Do I have the moon glow or whatever it's called?
Because I want to make spelunker potions now.
I gotta have some, right?
Let's see.
I do have some.
That's great.
Actually, I need to talk to Jeff.
Yeah, and I think I can give him moon glow.
I don't need to bring the potions.
Where's Jeff?
There you are.
Remind me?
Wait.
Wait, what?
Why are there two of them?
Oh, platinum or gold?
Ah, okay.
Gotcha.
Moon glow and blink root.
Okay.
Let's make it.
Blink root.
That is that one.
Let's leave one.
And moon glow, let's leave one.
Yep, that seems good.
This one gets deleted.
The strange plant.
Let's put the strange plant outside here again.
Or there, that's also fine.
The violent metal detector.
Fuck that thing.
It goes in accessories.
In you go.
Because I can actually use that to craft certain things.
Arrows.
Let's put that in ammo or ranged weapons.
So there.
Actually, I already have some.
Nice.
And now I click this button.
Oh, actually, not yet.
I need bottles.
Butters.
No, I need water bottles.
And then some gold or lead, right?
Let's see here.
Gold.
Go to the potion crafting station.
Here we are.
Let's go.
Ten.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, oh, this this system is fantastic.
I am so happy.
I can't say that enough about what I've done here.
It's just great.
And the best thing is, it's one and done.
I don't need to worry about this ever again, because I've done it now.
I just need to keep cleaning my plates whenever I use them, instead of letting them stack up, you know, until I do the dishes.
Fuck yeah.
Cheers to that.
Fuck off.
Wait a minute, I lost some gold.
How much did I lose?
Actually, I have no I don't have I had more than one platinum.
Did I lose more than a platinum?
Fuck.
I gotta find the one who took it because it's not on the minimap.
So that means a creature took it.
Actually, don't go don't go down this way.
This is too scary.
We're going here.
Did I put all these platforms?
I think I did a long time ago.
Oh, or a Calcom.
I shall be taking it.
It's also some over here.
Let me take that too.
Nice.
Okay, I think I'll activate the potion now.
Oh, wait a minute.
Did I?
Wait, wait a minute.
Why did the...
Why was the Spelunker potion sorted into chests?
Because I didn't have any in my chest.
I don't understand that.
Unless I'm blind here?
Was it sorted?
Oh, I did have one.
Ah, okay.
That makes sense.
All right, all right.
Now we're ready.
Now we are... Oh my God, this Spelunker potion, dude.
Best potion in the game.
That's awesome.
Let's go down here.
Oh, I should have maybe used the potion of return.
Nah, that's not worth it.
I was right here.
Not worth it at all.
Ah, not yet.
Further down.
Oh, dude.
Today I'm gonna make that Mage Tower.
It's gonna be so cool.
Is this where I died?
No, wait, this is some other time I died, I think.
Let's take this first.
Thank you.
And then...
Wait a minute.
I've been here.
Oh, we got a thingy.
Destroy it!
More Orichalcum.
Lovely.
Oops.
Wait, am I going the right way?
Yeah, I am.
Yep.
What's that?
Is that you making that sound?
Scary noises.
I will take this.
Hey!
There we go.
What's up, dude?
Oh, wait!
Soul of Night!
No way!
The ghosts!
I love it!
We need that shit.
I need all of it.
Let's put on the potion.
Uh, what is... mushy ladybug?
Let me quickly zoom out here.
Okay, I should be focused on getting my stuff back first.
Let's chillax for a moment here.
Give me that blink route.
Okay,
I should actually be zooming out all the way.
Don't die now!
In here.
Oh, this is so good.
I want to make a house made out of spelunker potions.
The walls are spelunkering potions.
You know, the roof is spelunking potion.
Everything is spelunking potion.
Don't think that's possible, but it would be cool.
Where did I go?
Down.
When in doubt, go down.
Oh, oh, that's cobalt.
Uh, what is that again?
Lead, okay.
I will recognize as soon as I see it.
Then I went here, heal up.
Let me grab this.
Recalled heart rate.
Nice, nice.
This is where I died.
So now it's time to figure out who has my stuff.
What is that?
Wait, what is that?
Oh, an amethyst.
Oh, okay.
Okay, uh, who has my stuff?
So hold on.
The thing said there was titanium nearby, remember?
When I was right here.
I cannot even see it now.
What the hell?
Where could it be?
I, I'm blind.
The metal detector said it was here, and yet I can't see it.
Also, my money is so sort of gone, I think.
Unless one of these creatures has it.
All right, keep digging down.
That's a boulder.
Just let this shit drain.
A strange plant, nice.
I don't even know what it's for, but I'm like, nice.
Uh,
man, this shit is rare, huh?
Oh, we got something over here.
Wait, I can't see shit.
Torch it.
There we go.
Let go.
Let's see.
Generation dynamite.
Uh, that's okay.
Oh wait, I'm about to die, I'm about to die.
Okay.
Uh, let's go down.
Oh, this is annoying.
Rock golem.
2000 HP.
Dude, I want to kill that.
But there's so much water here, I need to drain it first.
Let's get rid of this guy first.
Come on.
Oh, another one of these.
Man, this game is not making it easy, is it?
Wow.
Come on.
Oh, there's a thing above me as well.
There we go, he's dead.
Now we drain through.
Good, up.
Oh wait, this is draining way too slow.
There we go.
So that way, I can kill this guy now.
What's up, dude?
Wait, is he throwing things?
Oh, the fucking water is still here.
We gotta drain that too.
Drain it all, drain it all.
There we go, look at that.
He's throwing rocks at me.
I'm actually dying here.
Unreal.
Oh wow, the shot from off screen.
And I dropped, oh, what?
For fuck's sake, man.
I dropped so much money again, and it's gone probably.
Boy, is this fucking game punishing.
Die.
I really wish the money would automatically go into the fucking box.
Then I went this way.
Oh, it's such a long path down.
That sucks.
I haven't even found a single piece of titanium yet.
How is that real?
Uh, here.
I'm going super fast now.
I think I went here.
This way.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
I don't even care about that guy.
He dies from the stars.
Everything's fine.
This is a new place, whatever.
Just go.
I actually put this on.
Make a damn hole.
Let me throw.
Show me the titanium.
Oh, I'm actually taking this with me.
Yikes.
It's mine.
Okay, we're back.
Oh, I'm actually hitting him.
Out of mana.
Hit him with his insteps.
Yo, that works.
Not bad.
Fuck you.
Yeah, there it is.
Awesome.
Okay, let's see now.
This is where we were.
Did we get money back?
I don't think we did.
It's all over.
Put the money in there.
And then we open this.
And we deposit all.
Accept this.
And what else?
This one.
You feel vibrations from deep below?
I don't know if I like that.
I don't think I like that.
Oh my god.
Oh, just die.
I don't even know what's...
There's so much bullshit on my screen.
I can't tell what's happening.
Oh, look.
Right there.
Below me.
We found it finally.
That is it.
The titanium cometh.
Good thing I put my gold in the trough before I went.
That was a solid decision.
Down here.
I want to do fishing again.
I like the fishing.
There's no...
There's no projectiles trying to kill me, you know?
It's nice.
And you get items.
Pretty cool.
What's that?
Skeleton archer.
I also want to go back to the hallow and find more of those souls.
And there's actually so many things I want to do.
I have plans, okay?
Now, should I be worried about the round vibrating that they talked about?
That makes me a little bit worried, I gotta admit.
I think for sure the titanium is at a certain depth.
That's why I haven't found any so far.
This way.
Get rid of that guy.
There we go.
What's this?
That's crimp clean.
I will take it.
I wonder if there's still any use for that.
I should ask Jeff about it.
We just went through a biome change.
Uh-oh.
Wait, why is...
Oh, this stuff's still here.
That's interesting.
Nice.
Okay.
Be careful now.
Hit him.
Yeah.
Okay, now we drop and we do this weapon.
Don't shoot me.
Soul of Nice.
We got the money back.
Immediately put it in.
Nice.
Floaty gross.
What a name.
Flaregon.
I'll take that.
I'll take that on that.
Hello.
What's up, dude?
Oh, there's a guy here.
Another Soul of Night.
So this right here is...
Oh,
that's nice.
I don't want cobalt.
Nobody wants that.
I am above all that.
I don't do cobalt.
All right.
Bloop.
Nah, that doesn't work.
Man, these things drop off fast in water, huh?
Oops.
Hello.
Okay.
The mushy ladybugs are actually really annoying.
For some reason, they are always the one who ended up killing me.
I've noticed that in the chat, you know?
In the description every time you die.
It says, you were killed by...
And it's always mushy ladybugs.
So they must be doing something that I don't like.
Probably projectiles that I can't see.
Why can't I destroy that piece?
Oh, there's a tree.
Hello.
I kind of just want to kill these and keep getting Soul of Night.
Is that a bad idea?
Maybe.
Oh, I see.
Or it can't come.
He didn't drop any.
Okay.
This guy's gonna come over here now.
Okay, I think I'm gonna activate this again.
What do I see?
Nothing of note.
Zoom out.
Let's just take a quick look around here.
I don't see anything.
No, that's cobalt.
Nothing there.
Let's go down.
Oh, god.
Oh, my god.
I was almost stuck there.
Okay, so these guys dropped Soul of Night too.
Lovely stuff.
What about you?
Oh, he also drops it.
Hey-o.
Just murder everything.
I'm out of mana.
We got more.
This is the per- Oh, there's also some on the left.
This is lovely.
We're gonna have so much of this.
I'm excited, guys.
I'm excited.
Almost can't contain it.
Go here, grab that, and then we take this one.
What's that?
Eicher sticker.
I wanna kill it.
Let's do it gracefully here.
Be careful.
What's up, dude?
Let's not die to some random bullshit now.
Also, how much money do we have?
Let's put it in again.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
All right.
Let's kill these fuckers.
Oh!
Oh, they bounced three times.
Never mind.
I thought maybe these balls were disintegrated when they touched the red ore there.
That's not really how that works.
Oh!
I see you there.
Why do I walk into him?
That's kind of dumb.
Okay, zoom out a bit.
Okay, I think that's good.
This guy's gonna come here now, I think.
I'm scared of him.
This does almost no damage to him.
Notice.
30 damage.
And it's supposed to do...
Okay, 47.
So he absorbs a bit of it.
Oh my god, there's so many of them.
Come here.
Wait, I have bombs, right?
Let's bomb the shit out of them.
Oh wait, that's not really working the way I thought it would.
Let's go like this.
Maybe that's enough.
You know what?
It's fine.
Worst case, it will dig things for me, right?
All right, they took no damage from that.
I'll delete this little piece here, so that I can bounce it.
Oh, this little annoying piece right there.
There we go.
Bro, are you kidding me?
Oh, this weapon is annoying right now.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Oh, that looks pretty well.
They did shoot something at me that looked like it hurt a lot.
Oh, I'm dying, I'm dying, I'm dying.
What's happening?
What the fuck happened just now?
Crimson mimics.
He jumped through the bullshit terrain.
The fuck, man?
Wait, Eicher.
The blood of gods.
I remember needing this for something.
Okay, okay.
Calm down.
This is what we've been preparing for.
Oh, this is...
Wait, what?
Oh, never mind.
Loot all.
Delete and do this.
Wait, really?
Okay, delete.
Do I really not have any daybloom?
That's kind of incredible.
Oh well.
Just put these in here.
No, strange plant.
I feel like that's a weird item.
They go in here.
Get rid of the...
Ah, that's not there!
That's so annoying.
I hate dynamites so much!
It's the worst thing.
Okay, thank god there were no chests on the bottom row, huh?
Don't I...
I'm not missing some dirt here.
Let's just fill this up as well.
Oh my god, really?
One more?
There we go.
Okay.
That's something.
Cooking...
Oh my god, all the wall is also gone.
What a disaster.
My masterpiece ruined.
Did I do it?
Nice.
Okay, we're back.
Why do I have two looms?
Delete one of them.
Put that there.
Delete it.
Whoopee cushion?
I think I have one of those already.
Maybe.
Oh, I did some material.
Let's put it in here.
There we go.
All right.
I think it's time to experiment a bit with Jeff.
We're going to be experimenting on Jeff.
This looks good.
Yeah.
So, I want to bring him a bunch of things now that I want to test.
Obviously, we're going to take all the ore.
So, I must have a lot by now.
Let's see here.
Sort.
I taint 166 of that.
500 ore in Calcum.
Oh my God.
That's amazing.
Okay.
We can also take the silt, I guess.
Let's do silt.
Okay, so I want to take the ore.
And then I also want to bring him a bunch of accessories.
And a bunch of ingredients or materials that I found last time as well that I never checked.
So, I'm doing all of that.
In they go.
So, these I want to check.
This I want to check.
Wood is...
Turn it into...
Wait, what?
Where did I get that wood from, anyway?
Just make these.
Oh no!
Wait, wrong one.
Whoops.
I was like, that produced a lot.
But now I understand.
Mm-hmm.
Very good.
Let's see here.
I want...
I want, I want, I want accessories, I think.
No, this one.
What do I...
What have I not really checked?
Oh yeah, the metal detector.
And...
Remind me of that one.
I think that's it for this one.
Let me see, what else did I not check here?
Ranch tip.
That's not a material.
I think that's about...
I want to have two of these.
That's the cell one.
Sort.
Do I have duplicates?
No.
All right, let's check these off first.
Jeff!
Oh, there you are.
It's time, Jeff.
You need to tell me all about this metal detector.
Goblin tech.
I can make this.
I have a stopwatch, right?
DPS meter?
Metal detector?
Stopwatch?
Let's see.
Wait, no, uh, accessories.
Oh, I have a...
No, I have a platinum watch.
Oh no.
Fuck.
Maybe that works.
Let's try it.
Where the...
Let me try this one also.
Where the radio?
I have two of these.
Let's tell one of them.
Jeff?
Does this work?
Platinum watch, depth...
Oh, that's the one I need a compass for, right?
To make a GPS.
I also need to make that.
So I need to find a compass.
Okay, soul of night.
Let's see here.
Spirit flame.
Wait, that's like one of those little lamps with a genie in it.
Cool whip.
Dow of pow.
Soul of a night in a bottle.
Key of night.
Flesh cloning vat.
Uh...
Decay chamber?
These are all...
Special crafting stations.
Mechanical worm summons the destroyer.
And summons Skeletron Prime.
Magical harp.
Spirit flame.
I have no idea what this is.
Is this a ranged weapon or not?
It's dealing magic damage, but...
Does that mean it's melee or ranged?
I don't know.
Hold on.
I actually need a desert spirit lamp for this.
I don't have that.
Forbidden fragment.
Intriguing.
I almost have enough to make this.
I need one more soul of night.
Incredible.
Uh, okay.
That's cool.
Now I also want to check something else.
Oh, I forgot to check the icry.
But first, let's make this into titanium bars.
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute now.
Wasn't there a thing I needed?
Furnace.
Adamantite forge.
Okay.
Wait, titanium forge.
Titanium ore hell forge!
Oh, but I need a mythril anvil for that.
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
How do I make that?
Hold on.
Let's first check what the bars do.
Bars, bars...
Actually, hold on, I have some of this.
Wait, I have palladium.
Don't put in...
Give me that one.
Because I can make orichalcum bars.
So tell me what I can do with orichalcum.
Orichalcum anvil.
Used to craft items from mythril orichalcum, adamantite and titanium bars.
Will that suffice, I wonder?
Let's just make a bunch of bars.
Let's do this.
Turn them all into bars.
Whoa!
Damn, I have a lot.
Let's see here.
Where can I make it?
Here.
12 bars, that's easy.
Oh, wait a minute, I already have one.
I'm an idiot.
Fuck.
I already made one of these.
God damn.
Well, shit.
All right, I'm back, Jeff.
I fucked up, Jeff.
Jeff, what about the mythril bar?
Mythril anvil.
Fuck, how do I make a...
Wait a minute.
Hellforge.
Jeff.
Here we go.
Anamansite ore.
Okay, wait, mythril anvil.
I couldn't make that though, I don't have enough mythril!
Fuck!
I have five myth...
I need like 12, I think?
Shit.
Uh, wait a minute.
Do I have mythril ores, maybe?
Sort, let's see.
What do I have?
There's gotta be a way to do what I'm trying to do right now.
I refuse to believe there's no way.
So hold on, I need mythril bars.
How do I even get those?
From fishing, right?
I got those from fishing.
How do I get adamantite?
That's titanium ore.
I have that.
What about cobalt bars?
Was there anything in here?
No.
And this one, I can make the orichalcum anvil.
Craft items from mythril, orichalcum, adamantite, and titanium bars.
But, if that's with titanium, shouldn't that work?
I'm losing my mind, hold on.
It works!
Alright.
Why does that work?
Didn't it say mythril, uh, something?
It said mythril anvil.
Okay.
Well, there it is!
Put it down, dude!
Fuck yeah, here we go!
Okay, that's not a lot.
Thirty-four?
Uh...
Right, now I want to ask...
Let's ask the dude.
Jeff!
Look what I made!
Oh, here we go.
Damn, 23 defense!
Oh wait, this is for melee.
This is ranged, and this is magic.
But 15, that's already a lot better than what I have.
190% pickaxe power.
Ooh, I almost have to make that right.
Chainsaw, war axe, sword, trident...
Wait, frost helmet?
Frost?
Forbidden?
Magic and summon.
Huh.
Melee and ranged.
Hold on, what does this do that I can't do with this?
This can already mine everything.
I think I want to make the armor, dude.
I'm dying way too much.
Twenty-six!
Maximum mana by 100, that's actually kind of crazy.
And 13, oh no, I don't have enough.
I need to find more titanium.
Right now.
Holy shit.
Okay, at least I have a goal right now to what I want here.
I'm considering the summon stuff, but I don't really think it's that great.
The summons are kind of crap.
I definitely have to go for the titanium headgear.
If I put, yeah, I shouldn't make this yet, because otherwise I won't get the set bonus here.
So I should wait with that.
But I could make a... I could spend a lot on...
No, I don't need the pickaxe, actually.
I don't need that pickaxe right now.
I really don't.
Jeff, tell me about the weather radio.
I need a sextant and a fisherman's pocket guide.
Holy shit, I have no idea how to acquire that.
But I'm excited.
I probably get that from...
Okay, here's a guess.
I'm probably gonna get that from Izzy the Angler.
If I do enough quests for him.
Or I find it in one of the boxes I can fish up.
That's my guess there.
Displays the phase of the moon?
Oh, can I predict the blood moon then?
Is that what's happening here?
Is that why it's happening regularly?
Because it's every time there's a full moon or something?
Probably, right?
Maurice, you should buy something from me.
Wait a minute.
Oh yeah, there's also illegal gun parts.
I kind of forgot what that was all about.
I gotta buy that again.
Really, it's only worth 39 silver?
That's so sad.
Oh wait, this one.
For this one, I need reflective shades.
Counter curse mantra, the plan, and all this stuff.
Armor brazing.
No.
Oh wait a minute, actually, I actually have multiple.
No, I don't.
Where did I store extras?
Did I put them all in the box?
I guess I did.
Accessories.
Oh, there it is.
Yeah, so I need this one.
And I need the reflective shades and some other bullshit.
I should almost order these by what goes together in these boxes.
You know?
So I saw the recipe once.
Maybe I should put this next to this.
You know what I mean?
But I feel like that would never work.
Because then I accidentally click sort items and everything's fucked again.
So probably not, huh?
Put this in here.
And that.
These all...
Actually, Eicher!
Let's check the Eicher.
Eicher time!
Jeff!
What do we got?
A golden shower.
I can't make it.
I'm always short!
Eicher bullets.
Flask of Eicher.
Can be placed in water!
I kind of want that!
It makes...
Yeah.
I'm going to make a couple of those.
Ninety-nine of them.
I'm having trouble with my torches.
We're making Eicher torches, people.
It's happening.
And then we're also going to fill up this box with the oars.
Materials.
Let's fill this up.
Oh wait, I have stuff here!
Never mind.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on now.
Right, crystal shard, soul of light.
But I didn't have enough of this.
I remember this now.
I needed a little bit more of soul of light to do something.
I think I needed 15 or something for whatever the fuck it was that I wanted to do.
Now I got to go back down here.
We got to collect more of everything.
I'm so excited about everything.
In fact, I love everything.
Uh, maybe I should...
Dude, I want to make that tower, but I kind of want to go grab some more of that soul.
In fact, let's go to the other side.
Change of pace here.
I'm going to go to a Hello and see if I can find some more soul of light.
Motherfucker!
The evil is spreading!
Uh, where's Salva?
Oh, wait, it's Sylia now.
Oh, here we go.
What's happening?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
The darkness is encroaching.
My goodness.
Close that door.
Dude, we're going to get overrun here.
I need to buy more of the purification shit.
Where's Salva?
I need this.
I need a lot of it.
Oh, that's what I had on this keybind last time that I didn't have more of suddenly.
She is doing something right now.
Oh, it's a healing spell.
That's kind of cool.
I wonder if I can use that to my advantage.
Is she going to heal me with that?
I didn't pay attention just now, but...
Oh, God, the enemies are right at our doorstep.
Cleanse it!
Get rid of the evil.
We don't want it here.
Get rid of all of it.
Oh, my God, they do a lot of damage.
Well, I feel like a guy using a broom on a beach.
You know, I'm trying to broom the water back into the sea.
That's what that feels like.
I can't say it in English properly.
There's a saying in Danish for that, but...
It doesn't really translate very well to English, but I think you get the idea.
Get out of here.
These things are dangerous.
Okay, good.
All right.
Oh, I'm out.
Wait a minute, is my...
Hold on.
Where's my mana potion?
Oh, fuck, there's a cloud!
Bro, this place is fucked.
And we have this growling on the ground as well.
In fact, you know what?
Because it's growling here?
Let me try and dig down.
How about that?
Please fuck off.
Are these guys gonna drop any souls?
This is such a weird way.
I dug all the way around here and up here, but never actually...
250th crimeira.
Not bad.
All right, I've had it with this growling, we're going down.
Oh, shit, I can...
Oh, no.
I think I fucked up.
There we go, there we go.
Dig!
Oh, I'm digging!
Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Woo!
Okay.
I... Desert Spirit!
Is he gonna shoot some shit?
Uh... was he... what the hell?
Why is there grenades going off around me?
What the hell?
I don't understand the attacks of this guy.
Oh, it's the little purpley things.
I get it, I get it.
Oh, and they follow me.
I see.
Oh, this is... this is scary, dude.
I'm actually dead.
Yeah.
Bro, this game is way too hard!
What the fuck?
I can't kill anything!
What is going on?
Did I leave my potions here or something?
Wait a minute.
Mana?
I did leave some here.
Put them there, please.
Click on this button.
And let's move.
Delete all this bullshit, nobody needs it.
Alright, I'm going back to the hallow now.
Fuck that place, that's way too hard.
Clean it!
Lance!
Holy water!
Oh no, it's coming back.
At least I put it off for a little bit here.
It doesn't take that long to cleanse this.
But what about on the ground?
It's still all fucked up on the ground.
Maybe the system is that if there's more healthy tiles than there are non-healthy tiles, then the health will win, if you know what I mean.
Like, if it's over 50% of a given biome, then that will take over.
That's how that works.
Because right now I'm clearly not getting more than bare minimum here, right?
So the evil will always win sort of thing?
But how would I ever be able to do that?
Hello?
This thing reaches deep underground.
There's like no way, I would have to dig out the entire underground.
There's no fucking way that's how that's done.
That just makes no sense.
But here's the thing.
This right here is immune to it.
The hello is immune to the evil of the crimson.
So, what's up with that, huh?
That's like the good and the crimson is the evil.
I said that last time.
I want to go back down here.
That's the place.
That is the place where I found some stuff.
Oh no, I put all my potions in the... God damn it.
I auto-sorted them and they got into the box.
That's annoying.
This way?
Light mummy.
Are they gonna give me light soul now?
Come on.
It's always so violent when those stars fall from the sky.
Feels like I've taken a million damage, but it's actually just a bit of sand falling on my head.
Pixie dust, nice.
100 potion.
I will actually use that.
Nice to be able to see enemies.
Now we're at this spot.
Now you want some?
Let me go in here and then down.
That seems interesting.
And look at this.
I can place torches on the water now.
Isn't that... Oh no, this is bad.
This is scary.
This is a terrible place to dig.
Yeah, we can't get in there.
That's gonna take way too long.
Uh-oh, there's a guy behind me!
Kill him!
Keep going.
I'm gonna switch my torches out so that when I'm in water I switch to the other one.
Drain that shit.
This is where I got those crystal shards.
I forgot to ask the guy about these as well.
I did last time, but I forgot.
But I think there was something good.
I thought I could do with that.
Let's go down here.
In fact, I should just be killing things.
Because that's how I get the soul.
First we'll make it over here.
This right here.
Now we're talking.
This is the spot.
Is this where we died last time?
Probably, right?
What is that?
Prehistory preserved.
That's actually neat.
I'll take that.
I will take that.
I think I looted that box, I must have.
Hey!
Oh god, the cacti are really messing with me.
What is that?
A termite mound or something?
Oh!
Dreamer ghoul.
I need to kill these guys.
That was a big one!
I almost died.
Let's heal up.
Heal, nice.
Hey dudes!
It's not easy.
What do I even want here?
I'll take that and that and just...
I don't want any of this.
I guess I can sell that stuff, right?
Worst case.
Did I get any souls of...
I did get souls of light!
Let's just heal up a bit more.
While we heal, I'm gonna grab some more of this.
Let's get a lookout for some of that nice titanium as well.
What is that flower there?
Hey!
What did I just do?
Snake charmer, I'll take that.
Archery glow stick gold coin.
Open this now.
And fill it up.
There we go.
Whoops, shouldn't I open that?
Okay.
Do we see any ore?
Ooh, there's a lot down there.
How is that not hitting?
I almost just died.
Oh!
Look at this bullshit over here!
Ah!
I did do so much damage!
I need to upgrade my goddamn gear!
Hold on, before we go, I need the spelunking potions.
So I can find the stuff that I need to upgrade my gear.
Also...
Take all...
and click that.
Okay, that's good.
I'll take these potions back.
There we go.
Up here, we're gonna put this...
wait, no, this one.
There we go.
Scarab bombs, there's a nice...
Hallo torch?
Or a calico...
Why is that not getting in here?
Oh, because I made them all in the bars.
I'm trying to sell that.
And that, and that, and that.
Hey, buy this!
What do you sell?
Wait a minute, this is new!
You haven't sold this before.
You're selling new things now, Hallo.
Good on you.
Keep it up.
Well done.
You're the man.
Ah!
How dare you?
I just cleaned this place.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Okay, it doesn't work when you're up there.
Plants!
Good to know I can just keep running at full speed and this will still work.
It's a genius business strategy of Rosalva here.
Selling me this stuff when it always comes back, you know?
It's an unlimited money maker for her.
Very smart.
Okay, we're gonna play this more safe.
But I feel like I'm already doing that.
Like, I'm trying to hit things by bouncing things off shit, you know?
Being sneaky about it.
But sometimes it's impossible to hit anything, so you gotta open the floodgate, so to speak.
But then everyone comes out and...
And you're dead.
Wow, what just happened?
Oh, a worm came at the same time there.
That's what happened.
The timing on that, though.
Wow.
Always shooting arrows that I can barely see.
Okay, go this way.
I kinda wanna drain this.
I don't know why, but I want to.
Let's do it.
I feel good about this draining situation.
This draining makes me happy.
Drain it all.
Draining is fun.
Draining is good for the soul.
Ancient cloth.
That's kinda rare.
Only found, like, one of those so far.
Like, there's a soul of light just there.
Another one!
I'd be getting lucky.
Nice.
Actually, I'm gonna keep... I'm gonna kill these one by one.
Look at this, they drop soul of light.
I'm gonna take the easy pickings here.
Sand poacher.
Thank you!
Lamia.
I can also throw fireballs.
What a shot.
Come here.
Light shard.
I have some of those already.
I think I need more.
Oh, I'm getting so much soul of light!
Look at this!
Guys, it's happening!
I'm outta soul of light!
Feels so good.
Uh-oh.
The arrow people scare me.
Just die.
Play it safe.
Another soul of light.
We'll take it!
Look at that!
Look at the arc on this!
Isn't that glorious?
Ho ho ho ho ho ho!
Nice.
Getting so much stuff right now.
Feels good.
Alright, we gotta be careful.
We died somewhere around here last time.
Let me see if I can't kill these guys from up here.
Look at that!
Just fill up that room.
And then while I'm doing that, I can kill this guy.
Recharge.
Good.
Good, good, good, good, good.
More soul of light.
We got so much.
Like, look, ten so far.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, get away from me.
Another soul- Oh my god, we're swimming in it!
Put on your swimming trunks!
Lamia, we're going swimming.
Everyone's invited.
Yeah, you like that?
Everyone dies.
Oh, those are mine.
I thought the enemy was throwing those.
Off you go.
Look how little damage this does compared to the other one, the mythical flower of fire.
Oh, we've got a little party there.
Let's see if we can bounce some shit up there.
We're bouncing!
Isn't that just beautiful?
Hell yeah.
Hell yeah, dude.
You want some?
Those guys are very weak.
Oh, wait, we've got a chaos elemental.
Let's kill him.
Come here.
There we go.
Give me that soul.
I'm going to have so much of that.
I will never be out of soul.
Never again will I be standing on the crafting screen thinking, God, I wish I had more soul.
Because I'm going to have so much soul.
You can call me soul Goodman.
I'm also kind of looking out for the stuff I need to mine.
Let me actually activate that.
Maybe I'm blind.
Whoa.
There we go.
It's not hitting anything.
I thought it was dead.
Ancient horn.
No way.
Dude, this is what...
You run super quick on this.
What the fuck?
I thought this shit was cosmetic.
I mean, just like the bubblegum thing I had earlier.
Well, it's not quite cosmetic, but I thought I didn't think I could get more speed out of this.
This is amazing.
Fuck yeah, man.
Oh, I'm so quick, boy.
Yeah.
I'm a mage on a goddamn... What is it called again?
I don't even know.
And I...
Basilisk.
Well, I am a little bit taller because I can't get through certain points that I could get through before.
How's that not being activated, huh?
Please die.
Oh, we've got incoming.
Wait, does this do damage when I charge them?
Oh, be careful.
The mobility now is sick.
Fuck you.
No, no.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Formula One.
Dig, dig, dig.
Uh oh.
I think I'm dead, I think I'm dead.
I'm stuck between a...
Hey!
Cutting it close.
Get on the basilisk.
So many enemies.
Oh my god, yeah, now we're cooking with diesel.
Also, let's see the ores here.
Uh, not seeing anything of note.
Ah, here we go.
Yeah, this is not worth it.
This one is the way to... This one is the way to go.
For sure.
I'm getting a lot better at combat, I feel like.
It's like... It's like happening, you know?
This is not bad.
Wait a minute, I need to go here.
Dig, dig, dig, dig.
What did you say, get banana spirit?
What was that?
Oh, banana split!
That's actually my favorite dessert in real life.
Ever since I was a wee lad.
What am I taking damage from here?
Crash into anyone and everyone!
Oh, yeah, I'm kind of scared of crashing into things to see if I actually take damage.
Or maybe you need a certain speed first.
Gotta accelerate up.
Whoa!
Get rid of these.
There we go.
Heal up.
Keep going.
Oh, there it is!
Titainum!
That's it!
Coming to my back.
Join the others.
More.
We're not done.
Wait, here we go.
We're back to where we were once before.
I see Titainum!
That's a big boy!
That was scary.
Ah, another one!
Holy fuck!
Wait, is that increasing my mining?
Is the banana split increasing mining?
I wonder.
It feels like I mined faster just now.
There we go.
Heal.
Good.
Okay, calm down.
What do we spot?
I see some over there.
Oh, yeah, you want some?
Oh, no!
I'm okay.
There we go.
Play it safe.
Oh!
Oh, I'm dead.
I think I'm dead.
Oh, I'm confused.
I'm confused.
My character's confused.
This is so awkward.
Just wait here.
Wait here.
In fact, let's... block that shit.
There we go.
What a run so far.
What a run.
Okay.
Sun Mask.
Cool.
You know what?
Let's put this here.
Antlion Swarmer.
Slimy Saddle.
Oh, wait, that's the one I had before.
Lamina Tail.
Oh, I got all kinds of shit.
I gotta explore my inventory soon.
Okay, heal up.
I think we're about ready to go.
Oh, again!
I don't get a second to relax.
I'm getting souls, though.
Here he comes.
Get rid of him.
Oh, god, I'm almost dead.
I'm dead.
I died from some kind of poison, I think.
I couldn't find the antidote, is what it said in the chat.
Amazing.
But you know what?
This is fine.
We had a good run.
It's time to explore what we can make with all the stuff we got.
This is fine.
All right, Jeff.
My dude.
Jeffy Boy.
What can I make?
23 souls of light.
Let's see.
I can make the key of light.
A sheik.
No, chick.
Chick?
I don't know how to say that.
This one is kind of nuts, but I'm not going melee, so fuck it.
Cool Whip.
46 summon damage.
See, that sounds pretty good, doesn't it?
The best one I had so far was like 16.
I'm leaning towards the Cool Whip.
And then we have the Sky Fracture.
Which is a melee weapon with magic damage, it seems.
Which, I guess...
Oh, I guess you could go a melee build.
But with magic damage, so everything scales with magic.
Right?
You could do that.
But then it costs mana to use.
61 melee damage, fairy bell, rainbow rod.
I'm tempted.
Can I make this?
No, I need Soul of Sight.
Crystal Storm.
Hey, I can make this actually.
Uses three mana only?
Dude, we're making it.
Wait, wait, wait.
What was the last ingredient there?
What was the last ingredient?
Wait, Meteor Staff.
Showers.
Meteors?
Ooh, uh-oh.
Ooh, I don't know.
I'm conflicted.
I guess I'm going to try and make everything.
I mean, at some point, I'm just going to try and make everything.
And compare.
I'm going to be finding enough Souls of Light in due time anyway.
Uh, I need materials.
Materials.
In a material world.
Soul of Light.
Crystal Shard.
In fact, give me...
I don't need... Yeah, give me these as well, I guess.
And that and that.
Didn't I have more pixie stuff?
Maybe not.
Oh, I already have one of these.
Let's sell that.
I got to talk to... Hey, no.
No.
Buy this.
Thank you.
Alright, Jeff.
Check it out.
Oh, should I just do it?
Oh, wait a minute.
The last ingredient was...
Spell Tome.
I have that.
I have that, actually.
But what is the other one here?
Let me see.
Meteorite.
I can also make... Oh, I need 10 pixie dust for that.
I don't have that.
Oh, shit.
Okay, so I guess we're making Crystal Storm.
I could also make Rain... Can I make Rainbow?
No, I cannot make that.
What is this?
Light Disk.
Greetings, Programs.
Now, this one... Oh, this is Melee.
Okay.
The fact that this has...
Magic.
I can also... You know what?
Let's make this one and make this guy... We can make both of these.
Crystal Storm.
And this, because I kind of want to get rid of our Magic Missile anyways.
It seems like...
An upgraded version of the Magic Missile, but it's confusing because it's like a Melee icon, so I'm not quite sure what that'll do.
Magic Weapons.
There it is.
My trusty, masterful Magic Missile has been serving me so well for ages.
It's finally time to let it go.
Wait, I forgot the Spell Tome.
Spell Tome!
Where did I put that?
It's got to be in materials.
Yeah.
I even have this!
Oh, wait a minute.
Didn't I just buy these from someone?
Is that why I have them?
I think I bought them from the Wizard person.
Let me actually just double-check that.
Yeah.
Look.
It sells the Harp and the Bell.
Oh, wait, wait.
It also sells... a Spell Tome.
Yep, I got it from him.
Cool.
All right, do I have everything now?
No.
Shifting Pearl's hands die?
Wait, Bookcase!
Wait, really?
Like this?
It works!
Let's try it.
Wow.
Okay, that's a very fast attack speed.
Holy shit, wait a minute.
We can test the...
Oh my gosh!
Where's my DPS meter?
Let's go grab that.
We got to actually test these weapons now that we make.
It should be in here.
Here.
There it is.
Put it there, I guess.
Wait, this is... do I actually...
What happened to it?
Did I just throw it away?
No.
Put it there.
Yeah, you don't even need to have this equipped either.
Can't I just have it here then?
I can't.
What the fuck?
So, okay.
Wow.
It needs to be in your inventory, not in the little thing here that would make sense.
To put it.
So weird.
Whoops.
Okay, that's not bad.
In fact, that's like pretty decent.
That's pretty decent, man.
And it takes a while to run Umm as well.
Not bad at all.
And also, we can give it to...
Where's the guy?
He's over there.
But we can give it to him and possibly make it better too.
Alright, let's make the next one.
Magic missile?
There's only one thing I can make.
Mythril anvil.
So will that also work with the...
Hello?
Fuck off.
Will that also work with this...
Why does that work?
That's so weird, man.
Alright, make it.
Alright.
It's a fucking magic projectile weapon.
Look at the fucking icon of it!
That makes zero sense, dude.
I'm glad I tested that.
Alright.
Actually, let's go to Fjell now.
Because I actually want to try both of these now.
We gotta teleport.
Fjell, my boy.
Fjell, will you take a look at my items?
Look at my items.
I need you to adjust my items.
Fuck, I actually forgot to check the DPS on this weapon.
I don't know if it's better or not.
Come on, get up there.
I'm getting pretty good at this part.
And then... Yeah, here we go!
Oh my god!
Oh wait, I can't fly with this.
Oh, that's the limitation.
Okay.
But you can sort of switch between these.
Look at this.
Oh my god!
You can make some sick combos.
Fjell, reforge.
This one.
Six gold.
Hurtful.
Eh, let's go again.
Furious.
That's not bad.
But 20% extra mana cost.
Let's keep that for now.
Let's see here.
Broke it.
Fjell!
I thought you were a master of your craft.
You broke it!
Now it's masterful.
So you were a master of your craft.
You just lied to me.
Thank you.
He's totally trolling me.
What the fuck?
Alright, let's have that and this.
I like Furious.
Actually, do I like Furious?
Fjell, once more.
Superior.
Not bad.
Insanely fast speed.
But can I make it even better?
Manic.
Oh no.
Oh no, I'm doing it again and again.
I'm an idiot.
Hey!
Totally worth it.
Worth it.
Nice.
Now we go back.
Actually, before we go back.
Simon!
Oh!
He's no longer Izzy.
I mean, competent fishing master that I've been looking for.
You fucker.
Are you selling anything new?
You are selling this, which is interesting.
It is intriguing, but...
Adios, amigos.
I'm back.
Let's test the DPS of this one, huh?
Let's see how much better it is now that I reforged it.
Oh, it's actually a lot better.
It was around 390 before.
It's almost 500 now.
450.
Oh, I'm using mana potions.
How about this one?
It's not as good.
Wait, is it even hitting?
It's doing more damage per shot.
Whereas the other one is more of like a constant stream.
They're both very comparable, I would say.
18 crits.
38% crit chance, though.
Not bad.
I guess I can get rid of this shit now.
Oh, but can I?
It is nice to throw this around corners, right?
And this one is honestly...
Wow, it actually doesn't even do as much.
That's incredible.
So this one is shit now.
Yeah.
That one sucks.
We can get rid of it.
Let's put this in our weapon box for now.
In you go.
Also, let me test this bad boy now.
Fuck yeah.
Cool.
Oh.
Hey!
Dude, I love this mount.
This mount is actually a game changer.
It's changing the game for me.
And we have a sun mask.
I'm a sun god.
Dude!
I don't know why I just had this idea.
Maybe if I wear this mask, I will be granted entry into here.
This almost seems like a sun temple.
Think about it.
Fried egg.
Put stuff in here.
Honestly, just click this button.
And we have miscellaneous.
Put this in here.
Oh, that's a vanity.
In, in.
And these...
vanity.
In you go.
This one also sucks now, I think.
Don't really want it.
Put it in.
And we have the ore.
We can actually...
make that now.
Do we have enough?
I don't think we do.
45?
Hold on, how much did it take to make?
Let's just double check here.
So I want this...
30.
Let's just make...
Let's just start off making these.
26.
Ah, we don't have enough, I think.
We have 6 left.
Ah, crap.
So hold on, if I put this on now...
Yeah, we don't see the set bonus yet.
The question is...
Is the set bonus actually even worth it?
Or is it better to just have this on?
That's like 5 extra defense.
One extra there.
The set bonus is like 14% less mana cost.
Hold on, let me put this back.
Yeah, that's actually not even that fantastic.
I'm going with this.
Yeah.
I'm doing that.
Armor.
In you go.
And then we put this in the oars.
We eat the fried egg later.
Let me do that.
Four of them is kind of useless.
No, it's not.
We're going to take them.
What do we have in here?
Let's sort this.
Good, I need to bring my potions.
Honestly, just bring all of them.
Otherwise, I keep stacking them in here.
A potion of return.
I believe that goes in here.
The flame lash?
Flame lash.
Ah, you know what?
Also these torches.
Put one of them in here.
Let's put these in here.
Ah, these in here.
We're going to use these up first.
There we go.
All right.
I think flame lash, I still want to keep.
For those situations where I don't have any other options.
The thing is, I can't really be as safe with these weapons now.
Because I can't sort of throw balls of fire into small corridors and have them bounce around out of range.
But maybe this increased DPS I have now is actually going to just kill shit for me.
Oh my god, shit is hitting us.
Actually, you know what?
I noticed something.
It reaches here and it sort of stops.
Because there's a hole.
Let's test that.
I'm not going to actually cure this now.
I'm going to wait and see if it will spread down along here instead.
And actually not cross the gap.
That's what I will test.
Uh, yes.
Oh, not bad.
What am I hearing?
HANO!
Oh wait, this is way better against these guys.
Holy shit.
Theory time.
These things I just killed are monsters of the night.
They drop soul of night, right?
But I made this weapon with soul of light.
So I wonder if that's doing extra damage to them.
And if this opposite is true for weapons made of soul of night.
You know?
Dude, this mount is amazing.
Holy shit.
It's a complete game changer.
Head up.
Haha.
Fucking so fast I can't even see what's happening.
Ew, ew, ew.
Oh yeah, you want to fight now?
Now I have weapons.
Ho!
Wait, what?
Oh, I'm dying, I'm dying.
Let me try this.
The hell?
Come here.
This one is a little harder to hit with.
But maybe it's just me who can't hit anything.
I'm hearing this shimmer.
Okay, we have to...
Menacing magic quiver.
Nice.
We have to use the potion now is what I wanted to say.
There it is.
Let's go.
Let's find some of that sweet, sweet titanium because we're almost there with the set.
Fuck you.
My God.
I can't even see him.
Uh oh.
Oh, we're draining hard.
Oh, what the hell is that?
It's a flying sword.
Enchanted something.
Oh, these bounds off the walls!
Oh, that's a game changer.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, okay.
Hey!
This weapon slaps!
I'm dying.
I'm actually dying.
I got to get out of here.
Fuck.
It's coming.
Come down, come down.
Okay, there we go.
We healed.
Zoom in a bit.
I can't fucking play when it's zoomed out.
Everything's too small for me.
Volpin has arrived.
And now the banana splits.
Actually, eat the fried egg now.
And let's look for that damn ore.
Oh, I'm confused!
I couldn't move my character!
I mean, I could, but it was confused, so I couldn't fucking... my brain couldn't think.
It couldn't work.
My brain couldn't brain.
I just activated the potion, damn it.
Alright, new plan.
We're going straight to hell.
Boop, boop.
Beeee!
They
can't even catch me.
Look at this.
Oh my god, it's so fast.
Okay, we're going here.
Straight down.
While we're falling, spelunking.
Let's keep an eye out on the way.
What do we see?
Let's zoom out while we fall.
Oh!
I think I'm dying.
Oh my god, dude, what the fuck?
That thing almost one shot me.
I just put on some new armor still.
Doesn't fucking matter.
Why is everything doing so much damage?
It feels like the armor I'm putting on has no effect, dude.
Like, what's the point even of this armor?
I should be able to take more than two hits.
Just get away with it.
You know what I mean?
Okay, so...
I don't even know.
Eat the banana split now.
I'm spelunking.
I'm putting on all the potions now.
Heartreach.
Mining.
Thorns.
Magic power.
Everything, dude.
Fuck, I have no healing potions like that?
Like regeneration?
I'm actually going to be shooting these down as I go.
I'm actually out falling these.
Okay, we've got that there.
Oh!
Eicher sticker.
It's inside the walls.
I'm so scared of falling down.
Oh!
Titanium!
Oh wait, it's coming for me.
Wow!
Look at the speed.
Alright, there's nothing in there.
Keep going.
What am I seeing?
Another one of those things?
Oh, here they come.
Crimson Axe.
Okay, let's calm down now.
Kill it!
There we go.
Soul of Night and Eicher's.
Beautiful stuff.
Come up here.
Okay, this weapon is pretty good.
I am liking this weapon a lot.
It's a good weapon.
It's doing good damage and that's something I like.
What do we have?
Nothing over there.
We keep falling.
Let's just grab that while we're at it.
I think we should put on the other potion as well here.
Obsidian Skin.
Seems like a prime potion to use right now.
What's happening?
Oh, it's the geyser.
Hey.
Oh, is this guy gonna come here?
What's up, dude?
Oh, but check this.
It will bounce off the walls.
Oh, we've got people incoming.
Yeah, you like that?
I love this weapon.
They're both fantastic.
Come on.
Okay, fine.
Oh, oh, lava.
Okay, we're fine.
How did that just break?
Oh, they're getting burned alive!
Look how many there are.
Oh, they're coming up here.
I'm actually sort of caught.
A little bit.
Holy shit, what a massacre.
Keep bouncing.
I'm gonna flood this entire...
Dude, you can sort of make a...
Like a dedicated trap for enemies with lava.
I wonder if I can pick this up with a bucket.
Worm banner.
Look at all this soul.
Oh, it's peeing on me.
Did you see that?
Dude, I wonder if that's a golden shower.
Did it just do a golden shower on me?
It looked a little golden, didn't it?
And it looked like a stream.
This is dangerous territory, holy fuck.
It's going well though.
I'm holding my own.
We heal.
Lava is draining.
Let's see what's up here.
Oh, another one of these.
Wait.
Wait, where?
Where?
There.
Oh, I'm confused.
I hate being confused.
Let's just wait it out.
Huh?
Damn!
Oh!
Falling from the sky.
Oh my god!
Come on.
Potion me!
Okay.
Uh, what else do we have here?
Ah fuck.
We're getting souls though.
We're getting souls.
Uh oh.
I'm scared.
Get rid of it.
This is awesome.
I am such a glass cannon.
It's insane.
A weak glass cannon.
What the hell's going on?
There's a giant bat party down there.
Uh oh, uh oh.
It's peeing.
The pee's real!
Oh!
Ho ho ho ho ho.
Somehow I'm still alive.
Let's keep going.
Gimme that.
Wait, did my potion wear off?
I'm so scared of these guys.
The pee they do is so much damage.
Ah, they can't quite reach this guy.
It looks like they have a certain range.
They can't even hit me from here it seems.
Nice.
Doing good damage here.
Oh, this is so much better than the other weapon.
What is it?
A crimson mimic.
Is that the thing that fucked me last time?
The thing that went...
Ah, yeah!
It jumps through everything!
Holy shit!
Bro, this is nuts!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're not doing that.
No, no, no, no, no.
Phew.
I got some soul of night.
And I have some soul of night at home as well.
Let's try it.
Soul of night.
Grab some stuff here.
Let's go experiment.
Okay, Jeff.
Oh, let me check the thingy.
Okay, it hasn't reached...
Ah, look at this.
Hold on.
It does look like this is sort of guarding against it.
Is this also spreading?
Let's pay attention.
This is at the...
This is at the left tree over here now.
Let's just remember that.
Oops, don't fall down.
Alright, Jeff.
Ah, tell me about...
Go away.
This one, actually.
Hey, I can make this.
Do I want to make it?
Future send.
I mean, I don't really use arrows.
But maybe I will one day.
I could make this.
To consume lights, wooden arrows.
Cool.
Soul of night.
Who is...
Splashing.
Who's splashing?
Alright.
It's you.
Kill them all!
Are you done?
Fucking hell.
My God.
Jeff, where are you at?
You're sitting right there.
Okay, soul of night.
Show me again.
I can make...
the cool whip.
Oh, I don't have a frost core.
I can make this, actually.
Onyx blaster.
I mean, it's made from the shotgun.
It has the same damage, but...
probably something else is better about this, right?
So, we gotta figure out what that is.
I can't make this.
Soul of flight, huh?
Summon...
Oh, is this just like the other spell I had, but with now better?
It's like, unholy fire.
Oh, I don't have cursed flame.
I don't even know what that is.
Oh, golden shower!
It's made with Eicher.
100% they are using golden shower on me.
Yep.
That's what that is.
They were peeing on me.
Freaking knew it.
I wanna try the onyx blaster.
I don't know if I have enough dark shards.
I do.
I have a shotgun, I have knight.
Let's try it.
Piss off.
In fact, I just wanna keep crafting anything I can, just to free up all the crafting materials.
All base components need to be converted.
You know?
So, where do I craft that?
Mythril Anvil.
It's so weird that it says that, but it's actually an orichalcum anvil.
Onyx blaster.
Let's see.
Oh!
Okay!
Very different!
But, wait a minute.
Oh, did I put my...
Also, I'm not wearing the right gear for this anyway.
So, it's not really a fair comparison here, but I just wanna get a ballpark.
Uh...
Where's my...
What was I looking for?
DPS meter.
That would be in here.
I just need to have it on me.
Bro, that's not bad.
That's kinda legit.
Although, it's much lower when you...
Actually, it's not that great.
It's not as good as my other weapons, but...
Yeah.
Fuck.
I guess I have to try with the other full item set to actually really make a fair comparison.
But it's pretty neat.
I like the way that feels, you know?
Let's put it here for now.
We're gonna be experimenting with that later.
Hmm...
Is this...
The handgun?
It's a material, actually.
Let me quickly remind myself...
What I can make with the handgun.
Hey, Jeff boy.
Jeffo.
Phoenix Blaster.
I can make this.
But is it really that good, though?
I don't even think it is.
Let's try it.
I have Hellstone bars.
I have plenty, I think.
Hellstone bar, yeah.
Easy.
Wait, whoa.
Oh, lava-proof bug net!
I think I want to make this instead.
Fuck yeah.
Get rid of the shitty bug net.
Where is it even?
It's not here.
It's somewhere.
Put everything back for now.
Hell yeah, dude.
Ah, let's make some Hellstones.
Oh, wait, can I use this to make Hellstones?
Oh, no!
I need another Hellstone forge.
I need to go find one.
Okay, I guess I gotta go back down to Hell then.
Let's get the Hellstone forge.
Shit.
Yeah.
Let's just do that.
Ancient cloth.
We have these two.
Oops.
Put them there.
Void bag.
Oh, the handgun.
Let's put that back and range it.
And then here we put...
Let me get rid of the masterful flamelash.
That's actually not good anymore.
It's shit.
Sure, do that.
Or maybe even here.
That way I don't have to.
These are the one and two on my weapons.
That seems nice.
Spelunker.
Nice.
All right.
I think I also want to try and craft the summon one that did 46 damage.
Because that seems pretty sick.
But we gotta go find the remaining titanium now.
We really do.
And maybe even some extra on top of it.
Because...
Then I can also try the summon set.
And go full ham with that and try all kinds of things out.
I just want to experiment with all the weapons.
Find something that I'm comfortable with.
Look at this!
It's not spreading here!
Look!
This is how you stop it!
You make a hole in the ground.
Hey!
Unless... Actually, hold on.
Oh my god.
I feel so damaged there.
That's unbelievable.
Unless it works...
Can you...
Give me a second!
Fuck!
Jesus!
Open the fucking door!
God damn!
What I was thinking...
If it spreads like this down here and then it goes all the way up here again to there.
If that's the case...
And I'll find out soon...
Then the solution is to...
Dig all the way down.
Because if you go to here...
Let's say you dig to here...
Then it spreads like this...
And it goes to the right again.
Right?
But we'll have to see if that's actually how that works.
Or maybe it's just a range thing.
Maybe it doesn't jump a certain amount of blocks or whatever.
I don't know.
Okay, what am I even doing now?
Let's go back down.
Let's find some titanium.
Yep.
It's titanium time.
I guess it is titanium time.
Let's try to find out where I want to do it.
Oh, I also want to try and make the key of light and key of night.
Because I think I know where to use them.
Maybe that's the next thing I want to do with those souls.
I'll have to think about it.
I keep forgetting I have this mount.
I think I just damaged it by running into it.
You know what?
Let's try going here.
Get rid of that.
More titanium!
Nice.
I want to go down here and fuck some shit up.
Also, it's flunking.
Let's keep an eye out now.
There's a traveling merchant that I want to check out.
But not right now.
Can this guy come down here?
Maybe he's too dumb.
Yeah, fuck him.
Do I see anything titanium?
I see Orichalcum.
Wait, no, that's not it.
Is that it?
No.
I keep mistaking platinum for titanium.
The nice thing about this weapon is they spread out a little bit in the direction that you fire.
So you always hit something.
Even if you don't have perfect aim like me.
Is that a weird flower?
It is.
Strange plant.
That's what I wanted to say, but I forgot the name of it.
What do we got here?
I'm just gonna dig.
Nah, that's bad.
This takes forever.
Let's go to the left and then dig.
Yeah, this stuff is hard to get through.
I'm just ending up in the same place as before over there.
Uh-oh.
Should be in a cave right about now.
Why not?
Ah, there it is.
I saw it on the map.
Uh-oh.
Oh, look at that.
Fill up the room.
I'm gonna go down here now and then back down.
In fact, I'm going all the way.
Please, no enemy on the way that will fuck me up instantly.
Oh.
Ah, I see.
I see something.
Oh, no.
I don't have fire protection.
Mistakes were made.
Titanium.
That's lovely.
I may even have enough now.
Well, let's not risk it.
Let's not go back just yet.
No way.
Get away from me.
I hate the little bitty animals that do a ton of damage.
We have a guy here?
Fall.
Ah!
Oh, my God.
I'm beset on all sides.
Okay, I for sure need something special here.
Uh, I need the potion of Thingy.
Potion of Thingy, quick.
There we go.
Oh, nice.
A lantern.
I can chill here a bit.
Oh!
We're back.
I need to find a Hellforge.
Leave me alone.
Guys, I can destroy these projectiles, at least.
That's nice.
Oh, that's a... thought it was loot.
What do we have?
Nothing there.
I may have taken them all, actually.
I don't quite remember what I did when I was here.
Do we still have the Spelunking on?
We don't.
Let
me see if there's any ore here.
In fact, I'm just going to scan the upper parts here.
Because it's so quick to move from left to right here, right?
So if there's something, it'll pop up instantly.
Whoops.
Uh, wait, is that glowing because I haven't opened it yet?
No, okay.
Oh!
Drop Soul of Night!
They have never dropped that before.
Maybe everything started dropping that after I unleashed evil forces.
Is that a weapon?
No.
Soul of Night, I'm getting more and more of it.
Not even what I'm here for, but I'll take it, you know?
Oh, you're right there!
Oh, Jesus, I'm taking damage from all kinds of things.
Dude, Magic Missile is actually better in this place.
Any good loot?
Is that?
It is!
That was a bit there.
If you're too close with the item here, it doesn't actually do any damage.
With the Masterful Sky Fracture.
What is that?
Oh, it's, oh, okay.
It looked like some kind of weird thingy.
Any forges?
No, just an evil piano.
Wait a minute.
Hey!
It worked!
Wait, where did the...
Fuck, where did the item go now?
Where did the bug net go?
Where are you going here?
Oh my gosh.
Just to pause it all, honestly.
Do that.
There we go.
Oh, I need to...
Can I summon this guy down here again by accident, I wonder?
I've killed him already.
That scares me a little bit right now.
Ah, here we go, look at that!
That is amazing.
Anything up here?
No?
I can't hit anything!
My aim is shite.
Hellforge!
Nice!
Let's grab a couple of these.
I like this painting.
Alright, I actually got what I came for, but I'm going to keep going to find more uh, latinium here.
I've been finding a lot!
Awesome.
I don't see anything more.
That looks funny.
Oops.
Oh my god.
Illuminate bat!
Wait, I'm slow.
I'm burning.
Oh.
Oh, is my thing not working anymore?
I have no more obsidian skin.
Ah, look at that!
Even more titanium.
It's definitely only very deep, that you find a lot.
I think I can confirm that.
With some certainty.
Oh, this is a big one.
Look at that.
Look how much I'm getting.
Very nice.
I have to do this.
No, I don't.
Because I don't have obsidian skin.
I was about to drain.
Oh, there's even more!
Look at that!
We're blessed!
Oh, lava!
No!
That's terrible!
It's okay.
At least we got some titanium.
Ha!
Okay.
What else did I get?
I got the Hellforge, which I can use now.
I kind of forgot what I was using, what the point of that was.
Why did I get this again?
Huh?
Wait, why did I get that again?
Oh, because I just needed a Hellforge.
That's why.
It wasn't to craft anything.
I mean, it is, but not to craft anything using the Hellforge.
I mean, it is, but not in that way.
You know what I mean.
I wanted to make Hellstone bars.
Let's actually do that now before I forget.
Hellstone!
Fuck, fuck.
Wait, what?
Oh, did we need lead or something along with it?
I have a memory of that.
Let's see here.
Let's try... lead?
Or was it lead bar?
I forgot.
No, fuck!
Ah, I don't know.
Fucking hell, Jeff!
How did I make those stupid bars?
Wait, it was Obsidian, wasn't it?
I remember now.
Well, let's test anyway.
Yeah, it was Obsidian.
That is what it was.
Obsidianum.
I have some.
Wait a minute.
Could I use this over here?
Let me check now.
Fuck!
I could have used...
the other one!
Ah, wow!
Wow!
God damn it.
God damn it, man.
That's... horrible.
I was just so sure... oops.
I was so sure all you needed was the hellstone to make the hellstone bar.
Like any other bar.
But nope.
Not this time around.
Hold on, let me actually fix this.
As much as I can.
Oh wait, do we have a thingy?
The blood moon is rising!
We have a thingy!
But now I have sick weapons.
Hold on, do this.
Yeah, none of these actually penetrate.
That's a bit of a... not great, is it?
I need a great penetration weapon.
Get off my lawn!
Hello.
Get away.
What?
The bride?
Wait a minute.
Didn't I kill a groom once?
That's the groom!
I got a top hat.
I think I already got that from the groom last time.
What the fuck, man?
This game is crazy.
Let me just regen some mana here.
I'm doing so much better against these enemies with this weapon.
Ah, I got a cloud!
I'm getting money here.
Holy shit.
Nice.
Wait a minute, is this traveling merchant still here?
No, he's not.
Unless he's somewhere else.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
What's that?
Oh, the clown!
He fucked me up last time.
Not this time.
Got him.
Rossella!
She's healing.
Is she healing me as well?
No, someone died.
Kill him.
Dude, this is like fucking home invasion.
Phew, B and E.
Forceful KO cannon.
I got something.
What's that?
A zombie.
What's up, dude?
Phew, those guys are scary.
When they piss on you, it's very hard.
That sentence could be misunderstood.
In more ways than one.
Whoop!
Come on!
Phew!
I'm getting better at the combat.
But maybe it's just me getting a better weapon.
I feel like I'm also better at dodging.
But by having a better weapon, you kill enemies faster and thereby there's less enemies, which means it's easier to dodge, so...
Could just leave some bias there.
Ah, it's the cloud!
Dude, I'm doing pretty well here.
Let me play with this a bit.
Wow!
Wait, Mimic?
Where?
I didn't even see it.
Is it invisible?
Where is it?
I don't fucking see it.
Is it right here or something?
What?
I almost can't see anything.
I can't hit anything.
Oh, look how many there are down here.
Well, the way to beat those clouds is just stay indoors.
Just like real life.
Oh, unless the cloud is indoor with you.
Angry Nimbus.
Bro, it just occurred to me.
That's why that thing that Harry Potter rides on is called Nimbus something.
Because it's like a cloud reference.
I didn't get that as a child.
It just hit me.
That totally makes sense.
I haven't seen that movie since I was a child, so...
I remember that very clearly.
Nimbus 3000 or something was the name of that.
Bro, when is this stopping?
Have we not had enough?
Ah, we've got clouds.
Oh, man, that thing is killing... Oh, my God!
Everyone's dying now.
I must protect.
Dude, Rossella's healing.
That's awesome.
Don't hit me.
I mean, I'm getting a lot of money out of this.
There's that.
Did I do it?
Ah, nice.
The 100th Blood Zombie.
What's this?
Oh, it's a gravestone.
I think Dawn is upon us.
Or maybe not.
It just kind of looked like it.
Oh, there's someone behind me.
Oh, my God, I'm almost dead.
Oh, is she healing me?
I think... I'm not sure.
It could also be the lantern I have hanging.
No, Rossella!
Oh, man.
Right as we ended.
Incredible.
Oh, well.
It is what it is.
Let's grab all the loot.
Speaking of loot, I got something.
Lots of rain hats.
Fuck them.
Had to sneeze.
Get out of here, squirrel.
Top hat, get rid of it.
Forceful KO cannon.
Shoots a boxing glove.
Wait, is that just like the harpoon?
It's like...
Melee damage.
Okay.
Well, all right.
Wedding veil.
Waf, tu, woof.
Mavvich.
Huh.
Will something happen if I wear the whole wedding set?
Wait, Ash?
Doesn't that go in here?
No, that was mush, I think.
Delete, delete.
Delete that.
We put it in here.
Like this button.
Everything goes in.
Hellfire arrows.
They go in this box over here.
Down there.
Okay.
Wraith banner.
Let's get rid of these hats.
Hello, torch off.
Wait, are they special?
Let or Nisa the Dryad.
We're back.
Uh, oars?
This is all vanity stuff?
Well, that goes in the vanity box.
This is a melee weapon, weirdly enough.
Oh, I guess so, because it's a boxing glove.
I guess that kind of makes...
Let's try something with these wooden arrows.
I have these shadow flame bows.
I just want to see if I can even craft this stuff.
Jeff?
Could I possibly...
Oh!
It's gotta be here.
Hellfire unholy.
Wait, what?
Shoot shadow flame arrows.
Well, I guess not.
Fucking hell.
Whoops!
There's no shadow flame.
Shadow flame.
I guess I have to find them in the wild.
That's such a weird bow, though.
Like, what?
So where did I even get that bow?
Did I get it in down below?
When I say down below, I mean all the way down here, probably.
Now, is there anything else I want to try and craft?
Wait!
Whoops.
Look at this!
It's reached here.
It hasn't reached water yet.
Let's just pay attention to that.
And also here.
This isn't going any further!
So it seems the living wood is sort of holding this back.
That's... kind of makes sense.
My God, I get such a fright when the stars fall from the sky.
That's actually one reason not to wear this fucking cape.
I hate that effect so much.
Like, the smallest thing hits you.
You hit a thorn bush.
And the fucking wrath of the heavens come crashing down and you're like, Whoa!
What happened?
Oh, it's just a thorn?
I see.
Like, come on.
Can I have a cloak without that effect, please?
Because I still want to look kind of dapper, you know?
All right, let's grab the ore and make the rest of the titanium.
Titanium, titanium.
There.
Make it.
Now!
Are you ready, kids?
Titanium leggings.
That's the one I'm missing.
Oh!
Whoa!
Attacking generates a defensive barrier of titanium shards.
Wait a minute.
Why do these not give...
...magic stuff?
I mean, nice, I guess.
I guess I'll find out what that means.
Where is it?
Maybe you need to hit something for that to work.
Man, where are the enemies when you need them?
Now the world is devoid of enemies.
Oh, wait.
Use this.
There should be enemies here.
Come on, enemies.
I'm in your territory.
There's nobody here now.
What the f...
This game sometimes is trolling me.
There's no enemies.
Come on.
There's one.
Aha!
Look at that!
Imagine if they absorb a whole hit, no matter the damage.
Let's try.
Oh wait, I have to kill something for it.
They don't last forever, it seems.
Goddammit.
Okay, so now...
Uh, okay.
Huh.
Alright, I'm not sure how good that is.
It doesn't really block anything.
But I guess I'll have to try that some more.
Now I also want to craft the other helmets.
I want to make...
How about we try some melee?
Huh?
I haven't even really...
23 defense, dude.
Look at this, look at the difference.
8 defense, 23.
Let's try it.
Attack.
Okay, this has the same set bonus.
And let's try a melee weapon.
What's the best one I have?
Maybe that one.
I can make a crazy ass...
What do you even call this?
A flail.
Actually.
I think I have the ability to make that.
Let's see here.
I think with these even.
Let me check with the guy.
Actually, maybe titanium even.
But I don't have enough of that.
I have 6 right now, that's not enough.
Jeff!
We need to speak.
Converse with me, guide.
Oh, there you are.
You're so hard to see.
Dow of POW!
Ooh, I can make this, I think.
Hello?
I can make this?
Oh wait, I need the...
Oh wait, where...
Didn't I...
Shit.
Am I missing them?
Didn't I have light...
Oh, did I use them all?
Fuck, maybe I did.
Where was it?
It's not in here.
They're not there.
Did I put them in here or something?
Oh, I actually have a bunch of stuff in here.
Shackle...
Nah, actually, loot all.
Press here, delete all the banners.
Butterfly, hell butterfly even.
Hold on, what can I do with that?
Hell butterfly.
Oh, a jar with it.
Wait a minute.
Oh, I think I used all the light shards I had.
Yeah, I used them to make this weapon.
That's what I did.
Okay.
I kind of want to go grab another shard then.
Shouldn't be too hard.
What about the Iker, can I make something else awesome?
See this one!
Melee and whip attacks decrease enemies' defense.
If I go melee, I could start using stuff like this.
On golden shower, maybe...
Maybe it's worth to do this.
Imagine you use that first.
So here's the thing, targets defense.
I think defense is something universal that works against any type of attack.
Even though it sounds to me like it's maybe only melee, because it's always like that in video games.
But if I use this first, decrease targets defense, and then go nuts with my other.
Right?
Wouldn't that make a lot of sense?
Spell tome?
I can actually buy that.
Hira'el!
Hira'el, give me that.
I'm going to actually... Ooh, I have the perfect way of testing this, by the way.
The target dummy.
I mean, it's going to use up all my Soul of Night, but you know what?
Fuck it, it's there to be used.
We're doing it.
We're doing it live.
Well, yeah, I guess we are doing it live.
Let's see.
Wait, do I not have everything?
I need it...
Iker?
Soul of Night?
Spell tome?
Oh, bookcase!
Right.
Okay.
This is a bookcase.
Right.
Let's try it.
Golden Shower.
Okay, okay, here we go.
So...
Let's do...
I thought I just hit Hira'el.
Oh, I need the DPS meter, fuck.
You know what, the DPS meter, let's put it on a separate loadout.
Even though sometimes I forget I have them, because they're on that loadout.
But I think in this case, it may be worth it.
DPS meter, put it on here.
Oh, no, no, because then I don't have my gear on.
Let's just put it there.
Whoop.
Okay, so...
It's like between 400 and 450, right?
It's like around 400, mostly.
Now...
First, let's check how much damage this even does.
It's like not that great.
It's like 200.
But
now...
It's worse.
Wait, what?
Oh, wait a minute.
Also, I need my other helmet.
I mean, not that it changes this, but...
500.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm not sure that works.
Let me try once more.
The thing is, I don't know if it still has the debuff then, or not.
Let me try this one instead.
So, I go close.
Wait, go here.
That's like between 300... No, it's between 400 and 450, right?
Now we do golden shower.
And then...
Literally no change.
I mean, maybe a bit more because I let it go for longer, but...
I feel like that's not working at all.
But maybe this is nice for some circumstances.
The fact that it has such a weirdly long range and it's like continuous.
It's worth experimenting with, I think.
But we gotta talk to Fjell.
Because he can make it better.
Fjell, my man.
In fact, is it still Fjell?
Has he survived all this time?
Uh, here?
Yeah, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It is still Fjell.
Hey, what's that all up to?
Have you talked to her about chat?
No, I haven't.
Re-forge my shit.
Look at the golden shower.
A lazy one.
That's all you can do?
A strong one?
You can do better than that.
I said you can do better than that.
There we go.
You did it.
Well done.
You are the master of your craft.
You prove it once again, Fjell.
The man of the hour.
Love it.
46 now.
Pretty good.
Hey, Seagull.
Ah, that felt good.
Alright, I've always wanted to do this.
There we go.
I have now relieved myself over the ocean.
I think it's time to go to Hello and make a tower.
Nope, that's not it.
Ah, right.
Alright, put this back.
Not there.
Put it here.
I'm going to save this mask.
In fact, I'm going to have this on me.
But...
Hey, that's actually great.
I can switch them like this.
Hot swap.
Huh?
Now magic.
Now melee.
Magic, melee.
No, wait, melee.
Magic.
No, melee.
Now it's magic.
There we go.
Alright!
Fantastic.
Put this here.
Strange plant goes in the strange box of strange curiosities.
Click this magical button.
Nothing happens.
It's not magical enough.
We need materials.
In, in, in, in.
Keep.
Ah, that's fish.
Fishing, fishing, fishing.
Fishing.
There.
In you go.
Cobalt leggings, they suck!
Get rid of it.
Titanium bars go in oars.
God, I love my organizational system right here.
It has changed everything for me.
Delete these.
Look at that.
Smooth and beautiful.
Exactly how I like it.
So, to make a mage tower, we're going to need wood.
Materials.
Wood, wood, wood, wood, wood.
I don't think I actually have wood.
Let's test!
Make one of these and click the button.
I don't have any!
You see?
Smart.
And these have not grown at all.
Useless saplings.
This one grew for some reason.
This is a nice house.
Someone should live there.
Gimme wood.
I think we're going to make it out of wood and stone.
Maybe a little boring, but...
I mean, that's how you make a mage tower, dude.
I'm thinking of the one from World of Warcraft.
The design of it.
It's loosely in my mind, but maybe I'll...
Adapt it and add more room.
Maybe like a little sort of house on the bottom and then a tower attached to the side or something.
Like a classical, magical setup there, you know?
Bro, will you just let me fucking get these wood?
Hold on, I have an idea, actually.
Didn't I have an item that could advance time?
I could just skip the night.
Close door.
That would be weird.
Did I... Oh wait, also I want to test this!
I was on the pirate map, actually.
Fuck, I don't know if I... Did I have this?
This thing.
I don't know where I put it.
Materials.
Oh, I have no idea.
No?
Wait, I have a grapefruit?
And I have a... Where did I get... Where did I get that just now?
Maybe something dropped it.
And you... I have two of these.
Let's sell one.
Do
I have it here?
No clue.
No idea.
It's up and away.
Jeff, I need you to tell me about...
this.
Exploding bullet!
Oh, by the way!
The shotgun that I had!
First off, we didn't have our ranged gear on, and we were also using shitty bullets.
So maybe that weapon will be able to do sick damage if we get the right setup going.
Right?
Like, for example, this... looks sick.
Explosion impact probably does damage to everything around it.
So I gotta try that.
Okay, buy this from me.
There you go.
What is that?
Just a book.
Alright.
I believe stone I have.
Stone.
No, that should be over in the blocks.
Oh wait, I actually have a bunch of stuff to experiment with.
So, the Mage Tower I'm thinking of, it actually has like a blue roof...
in the game.
Do I have anything blue?
Granite?
Fjell is throwing a party!
Granite is kind of blue.
That could work for the roof.
Hold on, I can die things, no?
Also, let me check.
If you take this...
smooth granite.
Let's try that.
See how that looks.
Wait, what's that?
Oh, I could... campfire.
That seems special.
Let's have one of those.
Let's make a bunch of this.
Yeah, that could work!
A little purplish, but that's fine.
Pretty cool for a roof.
Then I need just simple stone.
Come on, oh, there it is.
I have a lot.
Leave one here.
And leave one here.
And I guess leave one of those here as well.
No, the wood doesn't belong there.
What else should I need for that?
Stone, wood, and...
And then, then, then, then, then...
Maybe I'll just bring some stuff.
Something that could look cool.
I need the last, I think.
Actually, I'm not sure about that.
Pearl sand block.
Sun plate could also be kind of cool.
It needs to be a little wizardy, you know?
Ethereum.
It's a material.
Jeff, I hate that I have to walk to Jeff every time to check a combination.
I feel like they could have done this differently.
Like, are you kidding me?
Sure, we can make a bunch of... Wait, workbench?
Ectomist?
That's probably some kind of environmental stuff.
Jeff just lost a lot of HP.
They're having a party.
Mama always said you've got to put the pass behind you before you can par... Wait, who's that up there?
Hold on, hold the phone.
Is that the merchant?
Sart... Ooh!
Dude!
Eight... What is this?
I'll take it.
Rain bro's hood.
Panda ears.
Wow.
Lifeform analyzer.
Fake unicorn horn.
Okay, I don't want to buy this.
Yeah, that looks...
By the way, is there a... Can I quickly equip this?
No.
I have to drag it.
Oh wait, not there, not there.
Put it here.
Take this off.
Eh!
Alright.
Let me try this.
What the...
Whoa!
Yo!
That looks amazing!
What a cool weapon!
Dude!
I gotta try this... Also, remember, I could have melee stuff here too.
I don't have that, so it's not really optimized right now.
Like, it's not bad!
That's pretty sick!
And the best thing is, I think it penetrates.
Like, it goes forth and then back again, through everything, right?
Let's actually quickly check that, to be sure.
Yeah, look!
No, wait, 90?
No, wait, I need to test this again.
I need someone to be close to me.
Here we go.
No.
Oh, it only hits them once, okay.
Oh, wait!
He just took damage from hitting one of these!
Dude, this weapon is awesome!
Hello?
It's like a melee weapon, but it's not melee!
Hey!
That's frickin' awesome!
Everything I ever wanted!
And then I have a shit-ton of defense as well.
But I guess it is a little slow, if someone is right in front of you, you have to wait for it to come back, right?
I love the way it bounces off things.
Pretty cool.
I do want to try a whip as well.
Maybe the cool whip.
But I need souls for that.
That's fast attack as well, like a long range and stuff.
It's pretty cool.
And how are we doing with Crimson?
I think it stopped here!
And over here?
Steel has not progressed further.
So I think... I think we're good!
And if we're not good, we can just take a big hole!
Frickin' awesome!
Okay.
Build a tower, but next time.
Because now...
It's been a long time.
Actually, it's been three and a half hours now.
I'm not gonna have time to talk, guys.
I gotta go get some stuff done.
I just want to say thank you for watching and enjoying if you're here.
Inscription vid today, you betcha.
It'll be out as soon as I'm done with this.
Thanks for watching, people.
You guys are the best.
Have fun out there and enjoy this wonderful Tuesday, okay?
I'll see you next time.
Bye-bye!